MEHDI JAFARPOUR

Personal

Address

Saburtalo, Tanarishvili13O, Domes building,B4,99 0177 Tbilisi

Phone number

+995-557430307

Email m.jafarpoor04@gmail.com

Date of birth 01-05-1986

Place of birth Tehran

i∔ Gender Male

Mationality
Iran

LinkedIn http://linkedin.com/in/mehdi-jafarpourabb250135 I am very interested in increasing my programming experience, learning new things and participating in various projects and being effective. One of the most important abilities that I believe in myself is solving problems and find practical, realistic and low-cost solutions, which helps me in my career.

Work experience

Network Administrator

May 2012 - Feb 2016

Saipa (Vehicle Factory), Tehran, Iran

Head office network manager, doing website-related affairs, monitoring the connection of center office with main factory and solving the daily problems.

Freelancer Mar 2016 - Jul 2017

Tehran

Web developing and Designing

Executive vice president

Aug 2018 - Present

Shahrayn, Tbilisi

Sales manager and planner, web developing and network administrator. The company is not a big scale one and one person have to do different rules to help the company to grow

Education and Qualifications

Bachelor of Computer Network Engineering	2011 - 2015
Dacificiol of Compatci Network Engineering	2011 - 2013

Tehran Azad University of Islamic Republic of Iran, Tehran

MCSA,MCSE 2012 - 2013

Tehran Institute of Technology, Tehran

React js and Redux 2021 - 2021

UDEMY (online course), Tbilisi

Skills

Html5	••••
Css3, Bootstrap	••••
JavaScript Es6, jQuery	••••
React-js and Redux	••••
Jest(Writing tests)	••••
Adobe Photoshop Cs	